SERGEY RADKOV

Boise ID USA | (208) 371-3904 | radkovsn@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/radkovsn

https://github.com/eriixon

www.sradkov.com

Permanent Work Authorization No Visa Sponsorship Required

SKILLS

Languages

C# TypeScript JavaScriprt HTML CSS Java

Python

Frameworks

.NET ASP.NET Angular Angular JS Vue JS React Boostrap 3 &4 Semantic UI

Storage

Microsoft SQL Firebase none SQL

Tools

Microsoft Visual Studio Microsoft Visual Studio Code IDEA PyCharm IntelliJ IDEA Azure

Technologies

RESTful Web services

Node JS

Yarn NPM
Redux jQuery
Git Heroku
NumPy SciPy
Magento Pega

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

A software developer with 3+ years of experience and a reputation for being a creative and self-motivated problem-solver, a team player adjusting well to people and environment, with positive attitude, a quick learner who is committed to continuous learning and enjoys challenges, and a hard worker always willing to jump in and help out when needed. As a software developer I have a keen interest in technology, web and mobile applications and user experience.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Software Developer | Allata | Boise, ID | 12.2018 – now

- Developed complex corporate software systems with production quality deployment, monitoring and reliability
- Worked closely with customers to efficiently resolve issues
- Modified existing software to correct errors, upgrade interfaces and improve performance

Technologies: .NET, C#, Angular, TypeScript, MS SQL

System Architect | Ruletek | Meridian, ID | 04.2018 – 12.2018

Worked as part of a team to design, build, and support BPM applications for clients, developed system features and functionality out of user requirements, designed and develop user interfaces, followed design methodologies, completing applications using languages and software products.

Technologies: Pega 7.*, Robotics, C#, HTML, CSS, SQL

Back-End Web Developer | Neoreef | Boise, ID | 09.2017 – 02.2018

Developed reusable code and libraries for future use for the unique proprietary content management system, integration of user-facing elements developed by a front-end developers with server side logic.

Technologies: ASP.NET, C#, VB, SQL, JavaScript, JQuery, HTML, CSS

Web Developer | Saharacase | Boise, ID | 11.2016 – 09.2017

Developed a vibrant, secure website using interactive features and SEO best practices to optimize traffic, page views and the user experience (UX), develop product web templates for major online marketplaces.

Technologies: JavaScript, JQuery, PHP, HTML, CSS, Bootsrap 3, Magento

Web Developer | freelance | Boise, Idaho | 06.2016 – 11.2016

Created and maintained web pages using HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, AngularJS and Node.js, optimized web pages for mobile.

Technologies: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, JQuery, AngularJS, Bootsrap 3

Senior Product Engineer | Volvo Truck | Moscow, Russia | 2010 -2015 Promoted Volvo telematics services, established new consulting services

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

- Practical problem solver with exceptional attention to detail
- Strong presentation, communication and negotiation skills
- Demonstrated success in project and staff management
- · Ability to adapt to rapidly changing environments

EDUCATION

Back End with .NET C# Course | CodeWorks | Boise, Idaho | 2017

Web Development Immersive Full Stack Course | CodeWorks | Boise, Idaho | 2016 The leading premier coding bootcamp in Idaho.

Java Level 1, 2, 3 On-line Course

| GeekBrains | Moscow, Russia | 2015

The leading online coding school in Russia.

Master's Degree | Transport Engineering Economics and Management

State University of Management | Moscow, Russia | 1997 – 2002 Russia's leading university in the field of management education.